Robert Alsobrook

email: lastgulch@gmail.com

website: BuffBob.com

phone: 303-519-0549

Work History

1999-2018-- Bison Rancher

1993-Present-- Carpenter

1995-1999-- Founder-Owner of Backcountry Pizza

Personal Endeavors

2015-Present-- devoted volunteer for Wildlife 2000- a beaver relocation organization in Denver.

2010-Present-- donated over 50 bison to various Native American tribes for food and reintroduction efforts.

2005-2015-- Served on the board of the Southern Plains Land Trust. Hosted events and school groups.

20010-2017-- Provided care for Denver Zoo bison.

And other environmental issues

Education

University of Colorado- Boulder Chemistry BS, Biology BA

SUMMARY

After 25 years of hard labor and a severe back injury I thought I would learn another trade- programming. I have no relevant work experience in this field so I have made a website, BuffBob.com, that showcases my talents. I built the website using python and flask and maintain the server for it and other programs found at that site. It has links to other webapps, code projects, my github and dockerhub, and other links. I built this page to act as the main way to display my talents given that I may have arrived here from a different path than most and a resume kinda seems pointless. Might be interesting to check out what a guy like me can pick up from the internet.

Relevant Computer Skills

- * Strong Data Analysis and Python skills
- * Machine and Deep Learning with Tensorflow/keras, scikit-learn, and more...
- * Strong Core Java skills. Beginner experience with java web programming and Spring Framework
- * Open source GIS, remote sensing and imagery including lidar
- * Intermediate SQL skills and experience with postgres and mysql server management
- * The basics- git, Linux, servers, sql, docker, C, javascript and frontend, maven, ...

What makes me a good hire

I am a rancher and self taught programmer- a problem solver with an extremely unique set of experiences and skills. I work my 'arse' off.

Please visit BuffBob.com to see my work